A Guide to the Records of the Drug Policy Office of XXX, 1990-1994
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Drug Policy Office of XXX, 1990-1994
The Library of Virginia
35386, 35669
40 cu. ft. (80 boxes)
XXX
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by Governor xxx on 13 June 1997 (Accession 35386) and 14 January 1998 (Accession 35669).
Biographical Information
XXX
Scope and Content
Records, 1990-1994, of the Drug Policy Office.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series: Series I: Correspondence and Subject Files and Series II: Grant Files.
Contents List
- Series I: Correspondence and Subject Files, 1990-1994., Extent: 7.25 cu. ft. (21 boxes). (Box 1-21)
  The Correspondence and Subject Files series is housed in 21 boxes and is arranged into two (2) subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Correspondence and B. Subject Files. The series consists of budgets, clippings, correspondence, memorandum, publications, and reports.
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1988-1994, 2 cu. ft. (6 boxes) (Box 1-6)
    This subseries is housed in 6 boxes. Includes correspondence, budgets, clippings, memorandum, and reports.
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1991 January-June (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1991 July-August (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1991 September-October (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1991 November-December (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1992 January (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1992 February 3-14 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1992 February 18-29 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1992 March 4-13 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1992 March 16-31 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1992 April (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1992 May (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1992 June 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1992 June 16-30 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1992 July (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1992 August (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Ann Landers, 1992 August-September (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1992 September 1-28 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1992 September 29 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1992 October 5-22 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1992 October 23-30 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1992 November (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1992 December (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1993 January (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1993 February (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Senate Bill 974, 1993 February-April (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1993 March (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1993 April (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1993 May 3-19 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1993 May 25-28 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1993 June 2-11 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1993 June 14-28 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1993 July (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1993 August (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1993 September (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1993 October (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1993 November (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1993 December (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1994 January (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: Subject Files, 1990-1994., 5.25 cu. ft. (15 boxes) (Box 7-21)
    This subseries is housed in 15 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by folder title. Includes articles, brochures, conference programs, correspondence, memorandum, minutes, publications, reports, and videos.
    - Alcoholism, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Articles, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Baptists, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Bill of Rights, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - By Our Own Hands, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Calendar, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Citizens Forum of Hampton, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - CADRE (Commonwealth Alliance for Drug Rehabilitation and Education), 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - CADRE, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - CADRE, The Community CADRE Handbook, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - CSAPP (Community Substance Abuse Prevention Program), c. 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Council of Governments, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - C, Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Dept. for the Aging, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Dept. of Correctional Education, Drug Infusion Curriculum Project, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Dept. of Corrections, Model Comprehensive Substance Abuse Treatment Programs for Correctional Populations, Grant application (Federal), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
    - Dept. of Criminal Justice Services, Drug Law Enforcement Formula Grants (Federal), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Education, At-Risk Strategies, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Dept. of Education, Steroids Resource Guide, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Education, Youth Risk Behaviors Study, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, Drunk and Drugged Driving Prevention, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, Highway Safety Plan, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, Highway Safety Plan, Part 1 of 2, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, Highway Safety Plan, Part 2 of 2, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Dept. of Personnel and Training, Policies and Procedures Manual, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Dept. of Social Services, Parenting Drug Education and Prevention Program, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
    - DARE (Drug Abuse Resistance Education), General, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - DARE, The 1986/1987 DARE Program: Strengths and Weaknesses as Perceived by Recipient School Principals and Classroom Teachers, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - DFSCA (Drug Free Schools and Communities Act), General, 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - DFSCA, Biennial Performance Report, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - DFSCA, Conference, 6th Annual, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - DFSCA, Conference, 7th Annual, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - DFSCA, Forms (blank), 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - DFSCA, GEPA (General Education Provisions Act) 406A Data Collection, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - DFSCA, National Steering Committee, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - DFSCA, Non regulatory Guidance for State and Local Programs, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - DFSCA, A Study of the Drug-Free Schools and Communities Act, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - DFSCA, Title V, Drug Education, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - DFSCA, U.S. Department of Education, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Employee Assistance Programs, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Emergency Grants to Schools, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Factpack, Facts About the Commonwealth of Virginia, c. 1989 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Alliance for A Drug-Free Virginia, Flyers, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Alliance for A Drug-Free Virginia, Newsletters, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Award for Anti-Drug Efforts, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Governor's Award for Anti-Drug Efforts, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Governor's Council on Drug and Alcohol Abuse, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Governor's Council on Drug and Alcohol Abuse, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Governor's Council on Drug and Alcohol Abuse, Letterhead (blank), undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Governor's Youth Council, 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Graphic Communications, c. 1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - High Risk Communities, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - High Risk Youth, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Institute for A Drug-Free Workplace, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Intensified Drug Enforcement Assistance (IDEA), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Just Say No, International, c. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Letter file directions, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Livin' Large USA, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Mailing list, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Maryland, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Metro Richmond Coalition Against Drugs, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - National Drug Control Strategy, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 13-14)
    - National Drug Control Strategy, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Neighborhoods in Action, The Facilitator newsletter, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Performance reports, Requests, 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Presidential visit, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Press releases, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Project Streamline, 1991-1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Prom Promise, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Publications, Council on Coordinating Prevention, Prevention Funding Information Bulletin, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Publications, Dept. of Criminal Justice, Drugs in Virginia, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Publications, Dept. of Criminal Justice, Report, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Publications, Dept. of Education, Six Year Technology Plan, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Publications, Dept. Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, A Plan for Prevention Services, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Publications, Dept. Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Funding Sources for Prevention Programs, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Publications, Dept. Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Prevention Funding Information Bulletin, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Publications, Dept. of Planning and Budget, A Study of Prevention and Early Intervention Services in Virginia, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Publications, Dept. of State Police, Americans for A Drug-Free America, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Publications, Governor L. Douglas Wilder's Agenda for Virginia, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Publications, Governor L. Douglas Wilder's Drug Control Strategy, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Publications, Governor's Task Force on Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault on College Campuses, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Publications, Join Together, Who Is Really Fighting the War on Drugs?, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Publications, Southeast Regional Center for Drug-Free Schools and Communities, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Publications, State Council for Higher Education (SCHEV), Virginia Link newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Publications, U.S. Dept. of Education, General Administrative Regulations, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Publications, U.S. Dept. of Education, General Administrative Regulations, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Publications, U.S. Dept. of Education, General Administrative Regulations, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Publications, U.S. Dept. of Education, Growing Up Drug Free, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Publications, U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, Alcohol and Health, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Publications, U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, Treatment Services for Adolescent Substance Abusers, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Publications, U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, The Office of Substance Abuse Prevention (OSAP) Prevention Monograph, Communicating About Alcohol and Other Drugs: Strategies for Reaching Populations At Risk, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Publications, U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, The Office of Substance Abuse Prevention (OSAP) Prevention Pipeline, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Publications, U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, The Office of Substance Abuse Prevention (OSAP) Prevention Pipeline, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Publications, U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, The Office of Substance Abuse Prevention (OSAP), Prevention Plus II, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Publications, U.S. Dept. of Housing and Urban Development, Home Front newsletter, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Publications, U.S. Office of National Drug Control Policy, Federal Drug Grants to States, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Publications, Virginia, Budget Bill (HD 1), 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Publications, Virginia, The Constitution of Virginia, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Publications, Virginia Commonwealth University, Youth Life-Styles Inventory, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Publications, Virginia Council on Coordinating Prevention, 1992-2000 Comprehensive Prevention Plan for Virginia, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Publications, Virginia Summit on Drugs, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Publications, Virginia Summit on Drugs II, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Publications, The White House, President's Commission on Model State Drug Laws, Community Mobilization, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Publications, The White House, President's Commission on Model State Drug Laws, Crimes Code, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Publications, The White House, President's Commission on Model State Drug Laws, Drug Free Families, Schools, and Workplaces, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Publications, The White House, President's Commission on Model State Drug Laws, Economic Remedies, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Publications, The White House, President's Commission on Model State Drug Laws, Executive Summary, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Publications, The White House, President's Commission on Model State Drug Laws, Treatment, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Public Service Announcements, Tax credits, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Police, Public Educators, and Peer Counselors Utilizing the Leadership of Students At Risk (PULSAR), General, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - PULSAR, Training, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Reclaiming A Community, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Resource materials, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Robinson, Ronald, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Rural Grants, General, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
    - Rural Grants, Communities That Care, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Rural Grants, Special Training, 1993 June (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Southside Coalition, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - State Alliance Program, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - State Fair, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Student Assistance Program (SAP), General, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Student Assistance Program (SAP), General, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Student Assistance Program (SAP), General, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Student Assistance Program (SAP), Workshop, 1992 September-October (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault on College Campuses (SASA), 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault on College Campuses (SASA), 1993 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education, Acts/Amendments, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, The Office of Substance Abuse Prevention (OSAP) Regional Communications Workshop, 1990 Summer (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
    - U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, The Office of Substance Abuse Prevention (OSAP) Regional Conference, 1990 November (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Dept. Housing and Urban Development, Resident Initiatives Activities, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Dept. of the Navy, Drug Demand Reduction Task Force, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Treasury Dept., U.S. Savings bond campaign, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Senate, Report, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Public Education Network, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU), A Baseline Survey of Drug Experimentation and Use Among 5th and 6th Grade Students in the Commonwealth of Virginia, 1988 Fall (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Virginia's First Statewide Prevention Conference, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Virginians Opposing Drunk Driving, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Union University (VUU), 1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Videos (Box 21)
- Series II: Grants, 1990-1994., Extent:.
  - Adapts, Inc., 1987-1990
  - Albemarle County Public Schools, 1989-1990
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, General, 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Abingdon High School, 1992-1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Brentsville Middle-Senior High School (Nokesville, Va.), 1993-1994
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, William Byrd High School, 1992-1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Cave Springs High School, 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Clarke County Public Schools, 1992
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Craddock High School, 1992
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, E.B. Stanley Middle School (Abingdon, Va.), 1993-1994
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Franlkin City Public Schools, 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Gar-Field Senior High School (Woodbridge, Va.), 1993-1994
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Glenver High School (Salem, Va.), 1992-1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Halifax County Junior High School, 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Jefferson Forest High School (Forest, Va.), 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Jefferson Forest High School (Forest, Va.), Photograph album, 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, John F. Kennedy High School (Richmond, Va.), 1992-1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Liberty High School (Bedford, Va.), 1992-1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Marion Senior High School (Marion, Va.), 1992-1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Martinsville High School, 1992-1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Menchville High School (Newport News, Va.), 1992-1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Metz Junior High School (Manassas, Va.), 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, George H. Moody Middle School (Richmond, Va.), 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Narrows High School (Narrows, Va.), 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Northwood Middle School (Broadford, Va.), 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Norview High School (Norfolk, Va.), 1992-1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Paul VI High School (Fairfax, Va.), 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Roanoke County Career Center, 1993
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Awareness Week, Mini-Grants, Western Branch High School (Chesapeake, Va.), 1992
  - Alexandria City Public Schools, 1989-1991
  - Alleghany Highlands Public Schools, 1989-1990
  - Alternatives, Inc., 1988-1989
  - Alternatives, Inc., 1989-1990
  - Amherst County, 1989-1990
  - Area III, A Believing Community, Resource and Image Action Council, 1987-1989 (Folder 1-2)
  - Arlington, 1990
  - Bill of Rights, General, 1993
  - Bill of Rights, Bedford Middle School-Pennington Middle School, 1993
  - Charlotte County Public Schools, 1988-1990
  - Chesapeake Volunteers in Youth Services, Inc., 1991
  - Children of Alcoholics, General, 1991-1992
  - Children of Alcoholics, Bristol Public Schools, 1992-1993
  - Children of Alcoholics, Colonial Community Services Board (Williamsburg, Va.), 1992
  - Children of Alcoholics, Dept. Mental Health Mental Retardation SAS, 1991-1992
  - Children of Alcoholics, Dickenson County Community Services Board, 1991-1992
  - Children of Alcoholics, Franklin County Public Schools, 1992
  - Children of Alcoholics, Hampton-Newport News Community Services Board, 1992
  - Children of Alcoholics, Loudoun County Mental Health Services, 1992
  - Children of Alcoholics, Middle Peninsula-Northern Neck Community Services Board, 1992
  - Children of Alcoholics, Prince Edward County Public Schools, 1992-1993
  - Children of Alcoholics, Richmond Area Community Services Board, 1992-1993
  - Children of Alcoholics, Rockbridge Area Community Services Board, 1992
  - C.L.E.A.N., Inc., 1988-1989 (Folder 1-2)
  - C.L.E.A.N., Inc., 1990-1993
  - Colonial Coast Girl Scouts Council, 1989-1991
  - CADRA, 1991
  - CADRE, Accomack County, 1989-1990
  - CADRE, Buckingham County, 1988-1990
  - CADRE, Chesterfield County, 1989-1990
  - CADRE, Coalfield County, 1989-1992
  - CADRE, Danville, 1989-1991
  - CADRE, Eastern Shore, 1989-1991
  - CADRE, Essex County, 1989-1990
  - CADRE, Greene County, 1989-1990
  - CADRE, Hampton City, 1989-1991
  - CADRE, Hanover County, 1989-1991
  - CADRE, Mathews County, 1990
  - CADRE, New Kent County, 1990-1991
  - CADRE, Norfolk, 1991
  - CADRE, Prince William County, 1989-1990
  - CADRE, Staunton, 1988-1990 (Folder 1-2)
  - CADRE, Tazewell County, 1989-1990
  - CADRE, Tri-Cities Area, 1989-1990 (Folder 1-2)
  - CADRE, Virginia Beach, 1989-1990
  - CADRE, Washington County, 1988-1990
  - CADRE, State, 1989
  - CADRE, State, 1990
  - CADRE, State, 1992-1993
  - CADRE, Governor's Alliance Line, 1989-1993
  - CADRE, Governor's Alliance Line, 1990-1991
  - CADRE, Governor's Alliance Newsletters, 1991-1993
  - CADRE, Video production, 1990-1991
  - CADRE, Workshops, 1991-1992
  - Council on Child Day Care and Early Childhood Programs, 1991-1993
  - Connections (Catholic Charities of Richmond), 1988-1989
  - Connections (Catholic Charities of Richmond), 1989-1990
  - Craig County Alternative Youth Center, 1989-1992
  - Craig County Administration, 1991
  - Cumberland Plateau Regional Housing Authority, 1991-1992
  - Danville-Pittsylvania Mental Health Services Board, 1988
  - Danville-Pittsylvania Mental Health Services Board, 1989-1990
  - Daily Planet and Virginia Coalition for the Homeless, 1992
  - Department for the Aging, Aging and Substance Abuse COmmunity Resources Directory, 1990
  - Department for the Aging, 1991-1992
  - Department for the Aging, 1993
  - Department for the Aging, Brochures, 1992-1993 (Folder 1-2)
  - Department for the Aging, Video training, 1992
  - Department of ABC (Alcohol Beverage Control), 1989-1991
  - Department of ABC (Alcohol Beverage Control), 1992-1993
  - Department of ABC (Alcohol Beverage Control), Pamphlets, 1991-1993
  - Department of Education, First Annual Statewide School/Community Student Assistance Conference, 1993
  - Department of Education, Parent Education Training of Trainers, 1992
  - Department of Education, Youth Risk Behaviors Study, 1992
  - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 1988-1992
  - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Council on Coordinating Prevention Program Development, 1989-1990
  - Department of Personnel and Training, 1990-1992
  - Department of Social Services, 1993
  - Department of Youth and Family Services, 1990
  - Department of Youth and Family Services, Local Network Coordinator, 1991-1993
  - Department of Youth and Family Services, Substance Abuse Managers, 1993
  - Department of Youth and Family Services, Substance Abuse Programs, 1990-1992
  - DARE, General, Application package (blank example), 1991-1993
  - DARE, General, Coordinator positions, 1993
  - DARE, General, Training seminar, 1991 July 29-August 9
  - DARE, Accomack County, 1992
  - DARE, Albemarle County, 1991
  - DARE, Albemarle County, 1992-1993
  - DARE, Appomattox County, 1992-1993
  - DARE, Ashland, 1992
  - DARE, Bath County, 1991
  - DARE, Bedford County, 1991
  - DARE, Bristol, 1991-1993
  - DARE, Brunswick County, 1991
  - DARE, Buena Vista, 1993
  - DARE, Campbell County, 1993
  - DARE, Charles City County, 1993
  - DARE, Chesapeake, 1992-1993
  - DARE, Chesterfield County, 1992-1993
  - DARE, Christiansburg, 1993
  - DARE, Clarke County, 1993
  - DARE, Culpeper County, 1991
  - DARE, Culpeper County, 1992-1993
  - DARE, Fairfax County, 1992-1993 (Folder 1-2)